Geidel Guerra

Software Developer

https://geidelguerra.com

Summary

Self-taught Software Developer with several years of work using Laravel, MySQL, Bootstrap and jQuery, creating custom CMS and APIs. Recently switched to Vuejs and Tailwindcss to develop rich and dynamic frontend UI and Vuetify for backend UI. Enjoys the challenges that each project presents. Loves Javascript and the Node ecosystem. Scholar of Stoicism. Casual Gamer. Avid reader with the right book. Honest and straightforward.

Skills

- VueJs
- Laravel
- Javascript
- CSS
- HTML
- PHP
- Nuxt
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- Git
- Basic RESTful APIs

Other skills

Unity3D

Skills to develop

- NodeJs
- ReactJs

- Electron
- NoSQL database

Languages

- Spanish (native)
- English (good at reading, listening and writing, can improve at speaking)

Experience

Fullstack Developer at Artcrónica (Cuban Visual Arts Magazine)
July 2018 – Present

Fullstack Developer at Fábrica de Arte Cubano (Multi-cultural center in Havana)

December 2014 – June 2018 (3 years and 6 months)

Videogame Developer at Joven Club de Computación y Electrónica October 2013 – December 2014 (1 year and 3 months)

Education

Universidad Tecnológica de La Habana José Antonio Echeverría

Engineering, Information Technology 2006 – 2009 (didn't graduate)

Mártires de Chile

High School, Information Technology 2002 – 2006

Showcase

Alberto Hernández Reyes Personal Website (July 2018 – Present)

https://albertohreyes.com

Nuxt + Tailwindcss + Netlify

La Tinta Magazine Website (March 2018 – Present)

https://latintamagazine.com

Artcrónica Website (July 2018 – Present)

https://www.artcronica.com

Wordpress

Gráfica Interactiva 3 (Art presentation collaboration) (October 2017) Unity3D 5

Gráfica Interactiva 2 – Eyeife Special (Art presentation collaboration) (September 2017)

Unity3D 5

Gráfica Interactiva 2 – Eyeife Special (Art presentation collaboration) (September 2017)

Unity3D 5

Gráfica Interactiva 2 (Art presentation collaboration) (March 2017)Unity3D 5

Gráfica Interactiva 2 (Art presentation collaboration) (March 2017)Unity3D 5

Gráfica Interactiva 1 (Art presentation collaboration) (June 2015) Unity3D 5

Fábrica de Arte Cubano Website (January 2015 – June 2018) Laravel 5, MySQL